<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Jack Wang</title>
    <link>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jack Wang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 02:21:23 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Learning Day-2</title>
      <link>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/big-data/spark-learning-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 02:21:23 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/big-data/spark-learning-2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction After this article, I will record some experience of learning big data.
Content 1. Spark core module Spark Core: The most basic and core functions of Spark are provided in Spark Core
Spark SQL: Spark SQL is the component that Spark uses to manipulate structured data. With Spark SQL, users can query data using SQL or the Apache Hive version of the SQL dialect (HQL).
Spark Streaming: Spark Streaming is a component on the Spark platform that performs stream computing for real-time data, and provides a rich API for processing data streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Learning Day-1</title>
      <link>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/big-data/spark-learning-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 02:52:22 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/big-data/spark-learning-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction After this article, I will record some experience of learning big data.
Content 1. Data processing tool Spark and Handoop Apache Spark: Apache Spark is an open-source, distributed computing system designed for big data processing and analytics. It offers support for various data processing tasks, including SQL queries, machine learning, and graph processing, through built-in libraries like Spark SQL, MLlib, and GraphX.
Apache Hadoop: Apache Hadoop is an open-source, distributed computing framework for processing and storing large amounts of data on clusters of commodity hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TailwindCSS</title>
      <link>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/tailwindcss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:55:45 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/tailwindcss/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Tailwind CSS is a CSS styling library that provides us with all the building blocks we need to build custom designs without using custom styles.
Feature Tailwind will automatically delete all unused CSS when building production files, so its size in the actual production environment is very small, and it is considered to be the CSS style library with the most design sense.
Installation //Install Tailwind CSS npm install -D tailwindcss npx tailwindcss init //Add the paths to all of your template files in your tailwind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast,Slow pointer--Floyd circle method</title>
      <link>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/fast-slow-pointer-floyd-circle-method/fast-slow-pointer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 23:34:06 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/fast-slow-pointer-floyd-circle-method/fast-slow-pointer/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This article is about how to use double pointers to solve problems such as merge array
Problem details Leetcode 88. Merge Sorted Array Analysis and thought Because it is a sorted array, add pointers at the end of nums1 and nums2 respectively. The values at the positions of the two pointers are compared each time. Copy the larger number to the last bit of nums1. After that, move the pointer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merge Sorted Array</title>
      <link>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/merge-sorted-array/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 18:15:48 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/merge-sorted-array/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This article is about how to use double pointers to solve problems such as merge array
Problem details Leetcode 88. Merge Sorted Array Analysis and thought Because it is a sorted array, add pointers at the end of nums1 and nums2 respectively. The values at the positions of the two pointers are compared each time. Copy the larger number to the last bit of nums1. After that, move the pointer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL</title>
      <link>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/sql/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 01:51:14 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/sql/</guid>
      <description>SQL experience
When combining tables, the efficiency of simply using the where statement is lower than join, which is equivalent to full join left join (left join): Returns all records including all records in the left table and records with equal join fields in the right table.
right join (right join): Returns all records including all records in the right table and records with equal join fields in the left table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 23:06:51 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jack 👋 This is my first post. Welcome to my Blog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 21:48:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jackywang96.github.io/BlogSite/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jack 👋 👤 Currently Software Development Engineer at Department of Education Victoria.
📷 Enthusiastic in fitness, photography, travelling, reading &amp;amp; video games.
📄 Checkout my resume: English / [简体中文]
✉️ Contact me at JackyWangMel96@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
